Thank you for watching!
This time, Kaki Endo, a double center, challenged to climb the highest staircase in Japan located in Kumamoto Prefecture!
The two of them will have to work together to complete all 10 missions.
Once you fail a mission, you have to go back 100 steps.
The rule of hell is that you can't go on forever until you succeed.
Will they be able to reach the goal?
Last time, they failed on the first try.
The two of them are wondering if they could remember the order of the single songs.
They start running with uncertainty.
What was the second attempt?
On 11.
If I get this one wrong, do I have to go back?
There's someone I want to talk to right now.
It's not... it's a sun knock.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
Two people surrendering almost 600 steps early.
The pressure's on heavier than the two of us, but...
Don't play the mistakes
Yes, we have to make the best of it
We have to move on.
That's positive.
I wasn't planning on being stuck here like this.
I'll just accept the rule change that we don't have to alternate.
Third time's a charm.
Bulbul Curtain
Come on, shampoo
Run, Baishukku
Uniform no mannequin Kimi no na wa kibou
Girls Rule Baretta
Chikkitara katachika
Natsu no Huri & Easy
Life is Beautiful Taiyo no Hattori
Ima Talekimasu Darekasareru Darekasareru
14 Haru Zion ga Blooming Koro ni Koro
15 is Naked Sister
16 is the meaning of goodbye
17 is Influencer
The two over the liver then guessed the name of the song smoothly and
30 is like, that's rock, man.
31 is something you won't find here
32 is
The first one is
I dream twice
33 is the monogamous tengu
34 is the monoboly
good good good good
Thank you very much.
This rule is a little tough.
And soon we arrive at the 200th step.
The 200-step toilet.
There it is!
I have to put it there.
There was shampoo with hot water!
So cute!
I got two of them.
It's right where I left it.
I thought I did it.
Two hundred and thirty-three.
It's endless, endless, endless.
You're not here at this time, are you?
From here on, the usual monotonous pictures of hard but steady climbing will continue, so I'll just skip ahead.
I'm going to skip ahead and skip ahead.
I'm about elementary school age for you.
If it continues, you'll have a one-sided love.
I don't think so.
I don't want to continue.
Oh, man...
Whenever I see acorns... it reminds me of something.
When I was in elementary school...
We collected acorns together.
And we were putting them in a bag.
Insects would come out of the acorns.
Right?
Yeah, a lot of caterpillars were born.
You're in elementary school, you like bugs.
You like bugs?
Yeah, that's why we each had a caterpillar.
Oh, wow.
You didn't mind them?
Yeah. I used to put them in the eraser.
You're the same way.
Why are you the same?
It's not from Italaclar today.
And on the 832nd step, I ran into my second challenge.
Embarrassing.
How can you still afford it?
Let's match memories.
If you can match the answers to the questions better than you thought you could, you're in the clear.
If you want to, you can.
What's your favorite place?
It's gone.
It'll never match.
A place.
We can still find a place if we try.
It's not that hard.
I'll go to the meeting.
I'll go to the right place, won't I?
Yes, I am.
Yes.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
I heard you had an audition. Jingle, jingle, jingle.
Recently? No?
The latest one's your favorite.
You're trying to give us a clue.
What? Wait a minute.
Recently?
Do their memories match?
It'd be great if they did.
I'm sorry.
Seino.
A millicrystal stand?
I got it right.
Yay!
What's this?
Recently...
There's a station that sells a lot of milk.
I like milk, and I've always wanted to go there.
I got up the courage to ask her out on my way home from work.
I have a memory of going home with him and talking about various things.
It's a place where we talked about many things together.
This is something that only the two of us can do.
I'm glad... I'm glad...
I'm glad we didn't go back up the 100 steps.
I'm glad.
And then they climb up to the top.
And they don't make you take a single step here.
I see.
That's great.
There's an upper level, too.
That's like 1,000 steps.
It's basically a climb.
Here we go.
I'm getting a little tired.
It's a little long... in the sky.
I love this jacket!
It's so cute!
I remember when we climbed Mt.
Fuji in the studio.
I remember when we were in the studio.
You don't know how hard it is.
Shitara-san said.
That's right.
But I do.
I guess we're just at a different temperature now.
It was less tiring.
And the 1187th step
Let's guess the answer of the double center partner!
The two of us say the answer to the question, and then the two of us tell the answer to the question.
I see.
Endo's most favorite food
That's a good one, right?
No. 1.
Milk, right?
That's disgusting.
Can I buy whatever I like best?
That's not the rule.
You can guess.
Two choices, two choices.
I wonder what Endo likes best.
I'm torn between two choices. Is one of them right?
Is one of them right?
I'm torn between two.
I see.
Can you guess Endo's favorite food, persimmon?
Curry and rice.
Ikeido.
I guess not.
Ike Curry Rice.
Ike!
Wow!
Nice!
Mitarashi dango and curry rice go well together
Whenever you have a mouthful of curry.
That's right.
That's right, so curry
If curry comes in catering or bento box, I'll definitely eat it.
So that's how it ends.
Thank you.
That's great.
What do you like?
Shrimp.
And again, we skipped about 400 rounds.
I mean goodbye.
There will be more cool-looking jackets from here on out.
More cool jackets.
We'll have more.
More and more
More jackets
The second challenge is
Here we go again.
Let's measure exactly 15 seconds with two people in the double center.
One at a time, without looking at the stopwatch.
Two people, totaling exactly 15 seconds.
"Exactly" means by five seconds.
Five seconds is safe if it's within a second of each other.
Okay, so 14 and 16 seconds is big.
Ten seconds is within a second of each other.
But it's still perfect.
But I was really good at that Wii Party game where you had to measure 10 seconds.
Then I guess we're good.
Ten seconds, one person sees five seconds.
Okay, let's do it.
I don't know if they're going to make it.
Eight, eight, eight, eight, eight.
Eight, eight, eight, eight.
Five seconds per person in eight seconds.
I didn't expect you to do that.
Five seconds for each of you in eight seconds.
Oh!
I got it!
I stopped at 8 seconds.
I thought that might be a little fast.
Okay, so just under 7 seconds.
Because that's what you've been working on at the Win Party.
Yeah, I've been doing it all by myself.
Can I see it?
Because the kaki's right.
Can you stop a Win Party oyster in its tracks?
Seven seconds!
Yes!
Here! You're slow.
I think it's good. It's slow.
Okay.
Fast! Fast!
A little over! Over 06!
Seven seconds and six?
Let's drop a hundred. Let's drop a hundred.
Can we go all the way down?
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 1 7, 18, 19, 20.
1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8,9,10 I'll settle for mine.
Because they don't come anymore.
That's right, I'm not coming back.
And after 200 round-trip steps, a challenge with a different theme...
Double center... Let's use the other's special skill to complete the challenge.
Double center Can you clear the challenge using either one's special skill?
Kakie's subject: Draw a portrait of a Nogizaka member in 15 seconds
The challenge was to draw a portrait of a Nogizaka member other than yourselves and two others.
If Endo can guess the correct answer, he will be the first to clear the challenge!
Who will Kaki draw?
Now, let's see who Kaki drew in 15 seconds!
Here we go!
Wait a minute!
I wrote something confusing.
Mannytail?
Yeah.
I don't have that image of a mani-tail, but I know what you mean.
I wonder if Endo got the message.
Did you get it? Really? Really?
I'm quitting Tsutsuya.
Correct.
That was good.
That's good.
And I wrote a long neck.
I should have written it all the way down to the shoulders.
The way you stroke it.
I should've even written how to stroke it.
You mean like a stroke?
Which mole is it?
It's on the other side.
It's on the right.
It's a shoulder.
Yeah, it's cute.
That's our eye.
Yeah, our eyes.
That's good. That's good.
Yeah, I'm so happy.
And they're finally halfway through.
I'm sorry about the gap.
It's a good thing there's a challenge.
If it wasn't for the challenge, I'd be really bummed.
I love it. - I love it.
I like this.
It's a mountain.
No stairs.
Mountain zone.
I see... the staircase floor version has nothing to do with it.
It's designed.
And 10 minutes of going down a path where you can't earn a single step...
It was placed naturally.
That's great!
From challenge to challenge
Jump 34 times with no mistakes.
One of you holds the jump rope, the other stands across from you, and the two of you jump together.
If you can jump 34 times with no mistakes, you're in the clear.
You know, I'm tired. I'm tired.
You two jump together.
They're trying so hard to be seen.
Before we jump together, let's see how good each of us is.
Thirty-four.
What the hell is this?
Four.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
He's about to take off.
I can't get my foot on it at all.
What the hell is this?
It's so cute!
Oh, it's good! It's good!
It's going down.
It's no good. Endo's here.
He's a little... floppy.
Can you make the jump rope challenge work?
Here we go.
Okay.
One.
Oh, wait a minute.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
I can't do this.
It's not something you two don't do together, Don Xaverby.
It's not what we do.
I'll try to get down there as fast as I can.
My 100-step return is the most time-consuming and strenuous of all.
It's the most time-consuming, energy-consuming, hellish journey.
You're an ogre, senting that way.
But me...
If you go there, you're going to challenge yourself, right?
Ever since I was a little girl... my mother.
She'd tell me I stunk of dong.
I'm sure I'd fall off my feet when I went for a walk.
And if I go to the river, I fall in.
I reek of dong.
I reeked of dong.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, my God.
You're kidding.
No, I'm not.
How can you make a joke like that when you're talking to Mr. Don?
He saw me, he saw me, he saw me.
You know what?
And now for the second jump rope challenge.
I've decided to take it any way I want.
Here you go.
Come on, come on, come on.
Slowly, slowly, slowly...
Rock, paper, scissors!
All together.
Come on!
in
One.
Oh, my God, I can get my computer out!
Oh, no!
The end is bad... the end is bad...
Oh, I quit end
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
I see.
I'll never seem to be able to jump rope, so I'll change the subject.
3-letter Shiritori at the dial center.
Eh?
Let's do 34 of them in two minutes, just the two of us.
But this one...
From the rest.
I can do it, I can do it, I can do it.
Let's get started.
Apples, gorillas, trumpets, parsley.
Ri, ri, ri, ri, ri, ri, ri, ri, ri, ri, ri, ri, ri.
Let's see...
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Ri, ri, ri, ri, ri, ri, ri, ri
There's one. There's one. There's one.
Oh, my God.
Ehhhh...
Huh?
What?
It wasn't a line break.
I know.
No? Maybe not.
And now we change the subject again.
For the fourth time, we're going to try jumping rope.
Oh, guess the other guy's answer.
Oh, good.
If you both guess the same answer, you're in the clear.
Yeah.
Only the oyster karaoke box.
Well, I've only said one of those in an interview.
Oh, well, then you're good.
You're right.
Oh, no.
You're going to match them, right?
You never know.
You'll get it.
Yeah, if we're going to sing together...
I'll sing along. It's normal.
Oh, yeah.
I'm going to sing this and win first place at the national festival.
I challenged myself to see if I could win first place.
Uh-oh.
Huh?
What?
Wait a minute. You got first place?
You got it? That's amazing.
I'll write that down. Hold on a second. Yeah.
I just need a hint.
I thought it was hard to sing.
I'll take a guess here. I don't want to go back a hundred steps.
I think only the core audience listens to it.
That's right, that's right, that's right.
I wonder if Endo got the right answer.
It'd be great if he got it right.
That song is so hard to play.
Mugs and sinks.
What?
Wow!
Yay, yay, yay!
We did it!
I sang!
I got the best out of the five of you.
What was the real box?
I like Eva too.
Lufran the Soul.
Who knows?
Lefranc of Souls.
That's all I know.
That's all you know?
And you two...
They're going forward with Nogizaka.
2000.
Synchronicity.
How are you doing?
The next challenge for these two is
Guess who is in the silhouette of the potential member's photo.
Mr. Himura is very bold in the silhouette quiz.
Can the two of you join forces and correctly guess three people within 34 seconds?
Let's just say if he says "bang" or something like that.
Lowey start!
Who is it?
Ume.
Isn't that Taction?
Nao Tomisato.
No, it's not.
It's difficult.
Who is it?
He's fast.
Yamamoto
Boy.
No, it's not.
Ume Ume
Umeme...
Umememu.
Oh, muzzy!
Well organized.
I sorted it out calmly.
That's why
Just in time when the time was up
Clear.
And the two finally
there it is!
The place we attended came
It was the first performance
The end cherry
The name is terrible.
I'll put "End Sakura" in there.
The fourth term students have just joined the history of Nogizaka.
Try your luck with a double center
There are 24 holes in the Blackbeard's Drama, and two of us take turns stabbing the 12 holes in half of them.
If you get stuck without blowing a Blackbeard, you're in the clear.
12 stabbings.
I think you're lucky, Saki.
What? No way!
Are you two really double-centered?
Okay, first shot.
May I?
Well, well, well... we're not there yet.
I'm scared.
Scary.
After that, they were able to keep Blackbeard at bay, and now they're down to just one each.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Line them up? Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
One more.
One more Endo, and we're all clear.
Why am I scared?
Endo has the last one.
He's got it whether he skips it or not.
I've got it, I've got it, I've got it.
The endo's amazing.
You ate the whole thing.
I've got it. I've got it.
I've got it.
Let's see how many steps you got left.
And then I tried again.
I tried again... to leave exactly 340 ml of bottled water.
This is interesting.
I'm up, I'm up, I'm up.
I'm so excited!
Wow!
Did we go over this?
Three hundred and eighty.
Well, it's not full, is it?
I don't remember where we were a hundred steps ago.
You thought I was.
I'm getting sick of this.
I'm halfway there.
You're halfway through your life.
You're being taught a lesson right now.
Right now.
It's teaching me.
A staircase to face yourself.
Thank you.
I think about it as I climb.
It's not like being the best in Japan.
I'm getting tired.
It's okay to be tough.
If you're not tough, you won't grow.
I see.
And now for my third challenge to the two of you...
Let's double-center and succeed at the same time.
You and I will hold a trash can between us.
Throw a rounded piece of trash from a distance of one meter.
If both of you can get it in...
That's another hard one.
That's a tough one.
Even for me.
You do this a lot.
Will we succeed in putting them in the trash at the same time?
You're so close.
If you reach out, you can do it.
I can do it.
Don't go too far.
Oh, I'm so nervous.
No, this makes me nervous.
I'm glad I didn't get off.
Thank you.
Third time's the charm.
We're finally out of the endless loop of challenges.
But...
But it's not a staircase.
Long designer staircase!
A long designer staircase.
We're not allowed to have these in the house, so they're not considered stairs.
Excuse me.
After that, we're just past the first endo center station.
From the alphabet.
Nagisa, name 46 current members.
Let's make up five names in less than a minute.
Choose one hiragana character at a time from the syllabary chart.
Make the surname of each member.
You can make 5 names within 1 minute.
Once you use a character, you can't use it again.
Find the characters that do not duplicate each other.
You can only use a muddled character once.
I can do it.
We can do this too.
Can we do it?
Can you two work together to make a name for your friend?
It's got two letters.
I'll take that one.
The black one...
You don't have to make others.
Ro is definitely stockless.
Kuro-Mi-Ne.
That's fine.
Three more.
Pretty much everyone.
Well...
Wait, wait, wait.
Black peas
Mizuki.
OK.
Wait... wait...
And... and... and...
One more.
Go!
I used... I used...
And used with...
Yes, yes, yes
who?
Aya, no!
yumiki
ami is no good
Surprisingly hard.
We don't have one more.
Nakanishi.
But there's no Ka...
There's no cover.
Wait a minute...
Wait a minute! Who's there?
Tsutsuki
Tsugui!
Edemosu...
There, there, there, there!
There, there, there, there, there, there.
yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Yes, yes, yes
Submerged
frizz
fountain (esp. a small one)
soooo
Wow!
That's amazing.
I can't make it because it's so quick.
Yay!
Interesting.
I'll make one dakten.
Sorry about that.
I'm sure everyone else will make one.
What the hell is this?
I'll write the end.
Can you make 5 names in the second try after this?
What's this?
huh?
This...
100 steps and back... and two of us will get our revenge.
You already thought of that, didn't you? Yes, you can do it.
Yamashita Yamashita Yamashita Sugawara
Sugawara, you used a muddle. Your right hand.
You've thought about it.
I've thought about it.
One more to go.
Here it is.
You need this?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Is it there?
Is he here?
I think we've been hit. I'd rather have Sato.
Someone get in here.
You want Sato?
Shit, we're running out of time.
Who's available?
What?
I'll take one.
Got it.
That's it.
Feels good.
It's more fun than I thought it would be.
Yeah, it's funny.
Happy guardians
The two of us here.
Me and Asuka.
Oh, yeah.
I'm going to like me.
I'm Finger's Kloster.
You're so cool, Saki.
Music video of the latest under song
Now on view
And
Mobile selection process for Under Live has started!
Next time
Did they make it to the finish line?
Hello, I'm Miyo Yakubou, a 4th term student of Nogizaka46
I'm going to a family restaurant with my good friends.
My favorite thing in the world is a family restaurant!
Please subscribe to our channel!